<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:itunesu="http://www.itunesu.com/feed" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>treasuredavisrealestateadvisors.com</link>
    <atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="treasuredavisrealestateadvisors.com"/>
    <description>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Treasure Davis Team - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <managingEditor></managingEditor>
    <lastBuildDate>2016-10-31 16:10:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <media:copyright></media:copyright>
    <media:thumbnail url="treasuredavisrealestateadvisors.com"/>
    <media:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Francisco, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</media:keywords>
    <media:category scheme="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">News &amp; Politics</media:category>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:email>homes@treasuredavis.com</itunes:email>
      <itunes:name></itunes:name>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author></itunes:author>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    <itunes:image href="treasuredavisrealestateadvisors.com"/>
    <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Francisco, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
    <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Colorado Springs Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:summary>If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Treasure Davis Team - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</itunes:summary>
      <itunes:category text="News &amp; Politics"/>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Latest Trends in Colorado Springs Real Estate</title>
        <link>treasuredavisrealestateadvisors.com/the-latest-trends-in-colorado-springs-real-estate.html</link>
        
          <category>Market Update</category>
        
        <author></author>
        <pubDate>2016-10-19 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <guid>https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Treasure+Davis/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate+Home+values+are+up+in+Colorado+Springs.mp4</guid>
        <description>

Today I want to talk about market conditions in Colorado Springs. I did some research recently and found some information that you might find helpful. According to the latest report by Keeping Current Matters, things are looking up for real estate this fall.

According to the numbers gathered by the Federal Housing Finance Agency, home prices have risen in every region of the United States over the last year. Every state is appreciating at a different rate, so even though your area might not be appreciating as quickly as others, there is still a very good chance that your home value has gone up.

If you want a more specific idea of how much your home has appreciated in our market, you can use our free home valuation tool. You may be surprised to find out what your home is really worth. As home prices recover and rise above their pre-recession levels, the real estate market will begin to normalize.

By the end of this year, home values are projected to go up by 4.1%. Next year, prices are expected to rise 3.7% before flattening to just over 3% from 2017 to 2019. This expected slowdown in home appreciation is the result of a normal, healthy real estate market.

“Now is a fantastic time to sell your home.”

As a homeowner, now is a great time to cash in on the equity you have built in recent years. With interest rates as low as they are, there is no better time to sell your home for top dollar and lock in an incredibly low interest rate on your next home.

Obviously, whether you’re ready to sell is completely up to you. I just wanted to let you know how favorable the market is for sellers right now. If you’ve been waiting for the ideal market conditions to sell, it won’t get much better than this.

If you have any other questions about our current market, give me a call or send me an email. I would be happy to give you more details!
</description>
        <enclosure url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Treasure+Davis/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate+Home+values+are+up+in+Colorado+Springs.mp4" length="" type="video/mp4"/>
        <media:thumbnail url="treasuredavisrealestateadvisors.com" height="72" width="72"/>
        <media:content url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/vyralmarketing/Treasure+Davis/Colorado+Springs+Real+Estate+Home+values+are+up+in+Colorado+Springs.mp4" type="video/mp4"/>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:subtitle>Learn all the tips, tricks and more for buyers and sellers in the Colorado Springs Area Real Estate Market</itunes:subtitle>
        <itunes:author></itunes:author>
        <itunes:summary>Recently, I did some market research and I found some information that you might find helpful. According to the latest report by Keeping Current Matters, things are looking up for real estate this fall. Home prices are up nationwide and they will continue to rise through the end of the year. Our market is returning to a healthy, balanced market, but if you’ve been waiting to sell your home, you shouldn’t wait much longer. To learn more, watch this short video.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:keywords>Real Estate for sale, Real Estate agents, top real estate agents, local real estate agents, find a real estate agent, houses for sale in San Francisco, home selling tips, home for sale, home buying, home buying process, property finder, property search, property, real estate market, estate agent, realestate, real estate listings, buying a house, homes for sale, mls, home buyer</itunes:keywords>
      </item>
      
    <copyright></copyright>
    <media:credit role="author"></media:credit>
    <media:rating>nonadult</media:rating>
    <media:description type="plain">If you are looking to buy or sell a home, get all the information and the latest updates, tips, and tricks from The Treasure Davis Team - your professional Colorado Springs Real Estate Agents.</media:description>
  </channel>
</rss>